What if only one star can shine?
The Cheetah Girls: One World is a family, comedy,
drama film directed by Paul Hoen.
Chanel, Dorinda, and Aqua are off to India to star in a Bollywood movie.
But when they discover that they will have to compete against each other to
get the role in the movie, will the Cheetahs break up again?
Chanel Simmons, played by Adrienne Bailon-Houghton.
Dorinda Thomas, played by Sabrina Bryan.
Aqua Walker, played by Kiely Williams.
Uncle Kamal Bhatia, played by Roshan Seth.
Vikram, played by Michael Steger.
Amar, played by Kunal Sharma.
The Cheetah Girls: One World (also known as The Cheetah Girls 3 or The Cheetah Girls
3: One World) is a 2008 American musical film directed by Paul Hoen.
It is the sequel to The Cheetah Girls 2 (2006).
The film premiered on Disney Channel on August 22, 2008.
It is the third and final film of The Cheetah Girls
trilogy, and the only film without Raven-Symoné.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
female friendship, rivalry, sequel, india.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.